http://www.nystrom.com/privacy

Nystrom is operating to support you during the COVID-19 pandemic. Read More
Sign In
Account
Shopping Lists
Cart ( 0 )
Cart ( 0 )
Checkout
0 items ( $0.00 )
View the Full Cart
1.800.547.2635
Nystrom, Inc.
X
Sign In
Account
Shopping Lists
Cart ( 0 )
Cart ( 0 )
Checkout
0 items ( $0.00 )
View the Full Cart
ProductsAccess DoorsStandardFire-RatedSecuritySpecialtyEntrance Mats + GrillesEntrance GrillesEntrance MatsExpansion Joint SystemsCompression Seal SystemsFloor SystemsWall + Ceiling SystemsRoof SystemsParking Structures & StadiumsFire Barrier SystemsFall ProtectionSafety RailingsGuardrailsSafety AccessoriesFire Cabinets + ExtinguishersFire Extinguisher CabinetsPortable Fire ExtinguishersDetention CabinetsFire Blanket CabinetsFloor DoorsFire-RatedDrainableNon-DrainableArchitecturalRetrofitWell HatchesSafety AccessoriesLuminous EgressHandrail ProductsDemarcation ProductsObstacle Marking ProductsDoor Frame and Door Latch ProductsSignageStair Treads + NosingsRoof HatchesPersonnelThermally BrokenDay LightingSecurityEquipmentRoof Hatch Fall ProtectionSmoke VentsStandardDaylightingAcousticalSmoke Vents Fall ProtectionStair Treads + NosingsEcoTread®PhotoluminescentSingle Part NosingsTwo-Part NosingCast NosingsWall + Door ProtectionCorner GuardsChair and Crash RailsBumper GuardsHandrailsWall CoveringsNew ProductsResourcesArchitect + Specification ResourcesArchitectural SpecificationsLEEDMasterSpec and BSDSpecification ConsultationRevit/BIM Design ToolsCEU Learning CenterProject Gallery Project TypesContractor ResourcesConcrete ContractorsFlooring ContractorsHeavy Construction ContractorsInterior and Finishing ContractorsMetal FabricatorsMechanical, Electrical and Plumbing ContractorsRoofing ContractorsGeneral ContractorsDesign Build ResourcesArchitectural SpecificationsLEEDMasterSpec and BSDPartsProductsRevit/BIM Design ToolsTechnical DocumentsWarranty DocumentsFacility Management ResourcesAccess DoorsCorner GuardsEntrance Mats + GrillesFire Cabinets + ExtinguishersHandrailsLuminous EgressPartsStair Treads + NosingsWall CoveringsDownload CenterCatalogsArchitectural SpecificationsMasterSpec and BSDLEEDTechnical DocumentsWarranty DocumentsCEU Learning CenterLiterature + Sample RequestsVideosAboutBlogCareersHistoryJames T. Nystrom FoundationLeadershipProject Gallery Project References
Access Doors
Entrance Mats + Grilles
Expansion Joint Systems
Fire Safety
Fall Protection
Floor Doors
Luminous Egress
Roof Hatches
Smoke Vents
Stair Treads + Nosings
Wall + Door Protection
Search Products
loading...
ProductsResourcesAbout
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
We hope that you enjoy using our website, safe in the knowledge that we are committed to protecting your privacy and security online.
Worried about providing us with information online? Let us put your mind at rest. Find out more about:
General Information
This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use and Sharing
Nystrom is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control of Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information, such as credit card data, that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the webpage.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Registration
In order to use this website, a user may be required to complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give certain information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact you about the products/services on our site in which you have expressed interest. At your option, you may also provide demographic information (such as gender or age) about yourself, but it is not required.
Orders
We request information from you on our order form. To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we’ll use this information to contact you.
Cookies
We use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.
Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site. However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.
Sharing
We share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.
We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes beyond filling your order.
We partner with various third party sales representatives to provide specific services. When a user requests a service that will be performed by such parties, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.
Links
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site, and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Surveys + Contests
From time-to-time, our site requests information via surveys or contests. Participation in these programs is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of the site.
Updates
Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 1.800.547.2635 or at
info@nystrom.com.
